{
  "2": [
    { "prompt": "je", "answer": "suis" },
    { "prompt": "tu", "answer": "es" },
    { "prompt": "il", "answer": "est" },
    { "prompt": "elle", "answer": "est" },
    { "prompt": "suis", "answer": "je" },
    { "prompt": "es", "answer": "tu" },
    { "prompt": "est", "answer": ["il", "elle"] }
  ],
  "3": [
    { "prompt": "j'", "answer": "ai" },
    { "prompt": "tu", "answer": "as" },
    { "prompt": "il", "answer": "a" },
    { "prompt": "elle", "answer": "a" },
    { "prompt": "ai", "answer": "je" },
    { "prompt": "as", "answer": "tu" },
    { "prompt": "a", "answer": ["il", "elle"] }
  ],
  "6": [
    { "prompt": "j'", "answer": "aime" },
    { "prompt": "tu", "answer": "aimes" },
    { "prompt": "il", "answer": "aime" },
    { "prompt": "elle", "answer": "aime" },
    { "prompt": "aime", "answer": "je" },
    { "prompt": "aimes", "answer": "tu" },
    { "prompt": "aime", "answer": ["il", "elle"] }
  ]
}
